A Guide to the Van Meter Family Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #7979
Van Meter Family Papers 1749-1872
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
7979
ca. 60 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was purchased July 6, 1965.
Container List
- Correspondence
  - Abraham Hite to Isaac Van Meter, 1788-1832; 6 items
  - William Millar to William Van Meter, 1858-1872; 13 items
  - Letters to Isaac Van Meter and William Van Meter, 1831-1872; 11 items
- Financial and Legal Papers
  - Financial Papers, 1856-1872; 10 items
  - Grants for War of 1812 Bounty Land transferred to David Van Meter for tracts in Illinois, 1853; 3 items >
  - Indentures (Deeds) between Garret Van Meter and Isaac Van Meter and others, 1775-1813; 6 items
  - Land Grants signed by Lord Fairfax, 1749-1778; 5 items
  - Land Grants signed by Beverley Randolph, Governor of Virginia, 1789; 2 items
  - Land Grant signed by James Wood, Lieutenant Governor of Virginia, 1794; 1 item
  - Land Grant signed by Robert Brooke, Governor of Virginia, 1796; 1 item
  - Land Grants/Warrants signed by Henry A. Wise, Governor of Virginia, 1858; 2 items